<problem>
  <p>You have launched an Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2) instance into a public subnet with a primary private IP address assigned, an internet gateway is attached to the VPC, and the public route table is configured to send all Internet-based traffic to the Internet gateway. The instance security group is set to allow all outbound traffic but cannot access the internet. Why is the Internet unreachable from this instance?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="True">The instance does not have a public IP address.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">The internet gateway security group must allow all outbound traffic.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">The instance security group must allow all inbound traffic.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">The instance “Source/Destination check” property must be enabled.</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>How can the domain’s zone apex, for example, “myzoneapexdomain.com”, be pointed towards an Elastic Load Balancer?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">By using an Amazon Route 53 Alias record</choice>
      <choice correct="True">By using an AAAA record</choice>
      <choice correct="False">By using an Amazon Route 53 CNAME record</choice>
      <choice correct="False">By using an A record</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>A company wants to implement their website in a virtual private cloud (VPC). The web tier will use an Auto Scaling group across multiple Availability Zones (AZs). The database will use Multi-AZ RDS MySQL and should not be publicly accessible. What is the minimum number of subnets that need to be configured in the VPC?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">1</choice>
      <choice correct="True">2</choice>
      <choice correct="False">3</choice>
      <choice correct="False">4</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>You launch an Amazon EC2 instance without an assigned AVVS identity and Access Management (IAM) role. Later, you decide that the instance should be running with an IAM role. Which action must you take in order to have a running Amazon EC2 instance with an IAM role assigned to it?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">Create an image of the instance, and register the image with an IAM role assigned and an Amazon EBS volume mapping.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Create a new IAM role with the same permissions as an existing IAM role, and assign it to the running instance.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Create an image of the instance, add a new IAM role with the same permissions as the desired IAM role, and deregister the image with the new role assigned.</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Create an image of the instance, and use this image to launch a new instance with the desired IAM role assigned.</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>A company has a workflow that sends video files from their on-premise system to AWS for transcoding. They use EC2 worker instances that pull transcoding jobs from SQS. Why is SQS an appropriate service for this scenario?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">SQS guarantees the order of the messages.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">SQS synchronously provides transcoding output.</choice>
      <choice correct="True">SQS checks the health of the worker instances.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">SQS helps to facilitate horizontal scaling of encoding tasks.</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>For which of the following use cases are Simple Workflow Service (SWF) and Amazon EC2 an appropriate solution? Choose 2 answers</p>
  <choiceresponse>
    <checkboxgroup>
      <choice correct="True">Using as an endpoint to collect thousands of data points per hour from a distributed fleet of sensors</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Managing a multi-step and multi-decision checkout process of an e-commerce website</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Orchestrating the execution of distributed and auditable business processes</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Using as an SNS (Simple Notification Service) endpoint to trigger execution of video transcoding jobs</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Using as a distributed session store for your web application</choice>
    </checkboxgroup>
  </choiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>When creation of an EBS snapshot is initiated, but not completed, the EBS volume:</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">Can be used while the snapshot is in progress.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Cannot be detached or attached to an EC2 instance until the snapshot completes</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Can be used in read-only mode while the snapshot is in progress.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Cannot be used until the snapshot completes.</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>What is a placement group?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">A collection of Auto Scaling groups in the same region</choice>
      <choice correct="False">A feature that enables EC2 instances to interact with each other via high bandwidth, low latency connections</choice>
      <choice correct="False">A collection of authorized CloudFront edge locations for a distribution</choice>
      <choice correct="True">A collection of Elastic Load Balancers in the same Region or Availability Zone</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>A client application requires operating system privileges on a relational database server. What is an appropriate configuration for a highly available database architecture?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">A standalone Amazon EC2 instance</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Amazon RDS in a Multi-AZ configuration</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Amazon EC2 instances in a replication configuration utilizing a single Availability Zone</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Amazon EC2 instances in a replication configuration utilizing two different Availability Zones</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>A customer wants to leverage Amazon Simple Storage Service (S3) and Amazon Glacier as part of their backup and archive infrastructure. The customer plans to use third-party software to support this integration. Which approach will limit the access of the third party software to only the Amazon S3 bucket named “companybackup”?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">A custom bucket policy limited to the Amazon S3 API in thee Amazon Glacier archive “company-backup”</choice>
      <choice correct="False">A custom bucket policy limited to the Amazon S3 API in “company-backup”</choice>
      <choice correct="False">A custom IAM user policy limited to the Amazon S3 API for the Amazon Glacier archive “company-backup”.</choice>
      <choice correct="True">A custom IAM user policy limited to the Amazon S3 API in “company-backup”.</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>An instance is launched into a VPC subnet with the network ACL configured to allow all inbound traffic and deny all outbound traffic. The instance’s security group is configured to allow SSH from any IP address and deny all outbound traffic. What changes need to be made to allow SSH access to the instance?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">The outbound security group needs to be modified to allow outbound traffic.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">The outbound network ACL needs to be modified to allow outbound traffic.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Nothing, it can be accessed from any IP address using SSH.</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Both the outbound security group and outbound network ACL need to be modified to allow outbound traffic.</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
