<problem>
  <p>You can modify the backup retention period; valid values are 0 (for no backup retention) to a maximum of ___________ days.</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">45</choice>
      <choice correct="True">35</choice>
      <choice correct="False">15</choice>
      <choice correct="False">5</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>If I scale the storage capacity provisioned to my DB Instance by mid of a billing month, how will I be charged?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">You will be charged for the highest storage capacity you have used</choice>
      <choice correct="True">On a proration basis</choice>
      <choice correct="False">You will be charged for the lowest storage capacity you have used</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>In the Amazon RDS which uses the SQL Server engine, what is the maximum size for a Microsoft SQL Server DB Instance with SQL Server Express edition?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="True">10 GB per DB</choice>
      <choice correct="False">100 GB per DB</choice>
      <choice correct="False">2 TB per DB</choice>
      <choice correct="False">1TB per DB</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>Which of the following features ensures even distribution of traffic to Amazon EC2 instances in multiple Availability Zones registered with a load balancer?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="True">Elastic Load Balancing request routing</choice>
      <choice correct="False">An Amazon Route 53 weighted routing policy</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Elastic Load Balancing cross-zone load balancing</choice>
      <choice correct="False">An Amazon Route 53 latency routing policy</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>You are building a solution for a customer to extend their on-premises data center to AWS. The customer requires a 50-Mbps dedicated and private connection to their VPC. Which AWS product or feature satisfies this requirement?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">Amazon VPC peering</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Elastic IP Addresses</choice>
      <choice correct="True">AWS Direct Connect</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Amazon VPC virtual private gateway</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>You are using an m1.small EC2 Instance with one 300 GB EBS volume to host a relational database. You determined that write throughput to the database needs to be increased. Which of the following approaches can help achieve this? Choose 2 answers</p>
  <choiceresponse>
    <checkboxgroup>
      <choice correct="False">Use an array of EBS volumes.</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Enable Multi-AZ mode.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Place the instance in an Auto Scaling Groups</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Add an EBS volume and place into RAID 5.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Increase the size of the EC2 Instance.</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Put the database behind an Elastic Load Balancer.</choice>
    </checkboxgroup>
  </choiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>Will I be alerted when automatic failover occurs?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">Only if SNS configured</choice>
      <choice correct="False">No</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Yes</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Only if Cloudwatch configured</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>When using the following AWS services, which should be implemented in multiple Availability Zones for high availability solutions? Choose 2 answers</p>
  <choiceresponse>
    <checkboxgroup>
      <choice correct="False">Amazon DynamoDB</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2)</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Amazon Elastic Load Balancing</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Amazon Simple Notification Service (SNS)</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Amazon Simple Storage Service (S3)</choice>
    </checkboxgroup>
  </choiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>How can an EBS volume that is currently attached to an EC2 instance be migrated from one Availability Zone to another?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="True">Detach the volume and attach it to another EC2 instance in the other AZ.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Simply create a new volume in the other AZ and specify the original volume as the source.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Create a snapshot of the volume, and create a new volume from the snapshot in the other AZ.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Detach the volume, then use the ec2-migrate-voiume command to move it to another AZ.</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>Regarding the attaching of ENI to an instance, what does ‘warm attach’ refer to?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="True">Attaching an ENI to an instance when it is stopped.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">This question doesn’t make sense.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Attaching an ENI to an instance when it is running</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Attaching an ENI to an instance during the launch process</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>You nave multiple Amazon EC2 instances running in a cluster across multiple Availability Zones within the same region. What combination of the following should be used to ensure the highest network performance (packets per second), lowest latency, and lowest jitter? Choose 3 answers</p>
  <choiceresponse>
    <checkboxgroup>
      <choice correct="True">Amazon EC2 placement groups</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Enhanced networking</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Amazon PV AMI</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Amazon HVM AMI</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Amazon Linux</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Amazon VPC</choice>
    </checkboxgroup>
  </choiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>You have an EC2 Security Group with several running EC2 instances. You change the Security Group rules to allow inbound traffic on a new port and protocol, and launch several new instances in the same Security Group. The new rules apply:</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="True">Immediately to all instances in the security group.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Immediately to the new instances only.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Immediately to the new instances, but old instances must be stopped and restarted before the new rules apply.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">To all instances, but it may take several minutes for old instances to see the changes.</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>A company is building a two-tier web application to serve dynamic transaction-based content. The data tier is leveraging an Online Transactional Processing (OLTP) database. What services should you leverage to enable an elastic and scalable web tier?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="True">Elastic Load Balancing, Amazon EC2, and Auto Scaling</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Elastic Load Balancing, Amazon RDS with Multi-AZ, and Amazon S3</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Amazon RDS with Multi-AZ and Auto Scaling</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Amazon EC2, Amazon DynamoDB, and Amazon S3</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>Your application provides data transformation services. Files containing data to be transformed are first uploaded to Amazon S3 and then transformed by a fleet of spot EC2 instances. Files submitted by your premium customers must be transformed with the highest priority. How should you implement such a system?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">Use a DynamoDB table with an attribute defining the priority level. Transformation instances will scan the table for tasks, sorting the results by priority level.</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Use Route 53 latency based-routing to send high priority tasks to the closest transformation instances.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Use two SQS queues, one for high priority messages, the other for default priority. Transformation instances first poll the high priority queue; if there is no message, they poll the default priority queue.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Use a single SQS queue. Each message contains the priority level. Transformation instances poll high-priority messages first.</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>Which technique can be used to integrate AWS IAM (Identity and Access Management) with an on-premise LDAP (Lightweight Directory Access Protocol) directory service?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">Use an IAM policy that references the LDAP account identifiers and the AWS credentials.</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Use SAML (Security Assertion Markup Language) to enable single sign-on between AWS and LDAP.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Use AWS Security Token Service from an identity broker to issue short-lived AWS credentials.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Use IAM roles to automatically rotate the IAM credentials when LDAP credentials are updated.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Use the LDAP credentials to restrict a group of users from launching specific EC2 instance types.</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>Which services allow the customer to retain full administrative privileges of the underlying EC2 instances? Choose 2 answers</p>
  <choiceresponse>
    <checkboxgroup>
      <choice correct="False">Amazon Relational Database Service</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Amazon Elastic Map Reduce</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Amazon ElastiCache</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Amazon DynamoDB</choice>
      <choice correct="True">AWS Elastic Beanstalk</choice>
    </checkboxgroup>
  </choiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>A customer is leveraging Amazon Simple Storage Service in eu-west-1 to store static content for a web-based property. The customer is storing objects using the Standard Storage class. Where are the customers objects replicated?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">A single facility in eu-west-1 and a single facility in eu-central-1</choice>
      <choice correct="False">A single facility in eu-west-1 and a single facility in us-east-1</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Multiple facilities in eu-west-1</choice>
      <choice correct="False">A single facility in eu-west-1</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>In AWS, which security aspects are the customer’s responsibility? Choose 4 answers</p>
  <choiceresponse>
    <checkboxgroup>
      <choice correct="True">Security Group and ACL (Access Control List) settings</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Decommissioning storage devices</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Patch management on the EC2 instance’s operating system</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Life-cycle management of IAM credentials</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Controlling physical access to compute resources</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Encryption of EBS (Elastic Block Storage) volumes</choice>
    </checkboxgroup>
  </choiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>If you’re unable to connect via SSH to your EC2 instance, which of the following should you check and possibly correct to restore connectivity?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">Adjust Security Group to permit egress traffic over TCP port 443 from your IP.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Configure the IAM role to permit changes to security group settings.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Modify the instance security group to allow ingress of ICMP packets from your IP.</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Adjust the instance’s Security Group to permit ingress traffic over port 22 from your IP.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Apply the most recently released Operating System security patches.</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>After launching an instance that you intend to serve as a NAT (Network Address Translation) device in a public subnet you modify your route tables to have the NAT device be the target of internet bound traffic of your private subnet. When you try and make an outbound connection to the internet from an instance in the private subnet, you are not successful. Which of the following steps could resolve the issue?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="True">Disabling the Source/Destination Check attribute on the NAT instance</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Attaching an Elastic IP address to the instance in the private subnet</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Attaching a second Elastic Network Interface (ENI) to the NAT instance, and placing it in the private subnet</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Attaching a second Elastic Network Interface (ENI) to the instance in the private subnet, and placing it in the public subnet</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>You have a web application running on six Amazon EC2 instances, consuming about 45% of resources on each instance. You are using auto-scaling to make sure that six instances are running at all times. The number of requests this application processes is consistent and does not experience spikes. The application is critical to your business and you want high availability at all times. You want the load to be distributed evenly between all instances. You also want to use the same Amazon Machine Image (AMI) for all instances. Which of the following architectural choices should you make?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">Deploy 6 EC2 instances in one availability zone and use Amazon Elastic Load Balancer.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Deploy 3 EC2 instances in one region and 3 in another region and use Amazon Elastic Load Balancer.</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Deploy 3 EC2 instances in one availability zone and 3 in another availability zone and use Amazon Elastic Load Balancer.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Deploy 2 EC2 instances in three regions and use Amazon Elastic Load Balancer.</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>When an EC2 EBS-backed (EBS root) instance is stopped, what happens to the data on any ephemeral store volumes?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">Data is automatically saved in an EBS volume.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Data is unavailable until the instance is restarted.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Data will be deleted and will no longer be accessible.</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Data is automatically saved as an EBS snapshot.</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>Which of the following items are required to allow an application deployed on an EC2 instance to write data to a DynamoDB table? Assume that no security keys are allowed to be stored on the EC2 instance. (Choose 2 answers)</p>
  <choiceresponse>
    <checkboxgroup>
      <choice correct="True">Create an IAM Role that allows write access to the DynamoDB table.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Add an IAM Role to a running EC2 instance.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Create an IAM User that allows write access to the DynamoDB table.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Add an IAM User to a running EC2 instance.</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Launch an EC2 Instance with the IAM Role included in the launch configuration.</choice>
    </checkboxgroup>
  </choiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>Your web application front end consists of multiple EC2 instances behind an Elastic Load Balancer. You configured ELB to perform health checks on these EC2 instances, if an instance fails to pass health checks, which statement will be true?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">The instance gets terminated automatically by the ELB.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">The instance gets quarantined by the ELB for root cause analysis.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">The instance is replaced automatically by the ELB.</choice>
      <choice correct="True">The ELB stops sending traffic to the instance that failed its health check.</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>What is one key difference between an Amazon EBS-backed and an instance-store backed instance?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="True">Amazon EBS-backed instances can be stopped and restarted.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Instance-store backed instances can be stopped and restarted.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Auto scaling requires using Amazon EBS-backed instances.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Virtual Private Cloud requires EBS backed instances.</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>You have decided to change the instance type for instances running in your application tier that is using Auto Scaling. In which area below would you change the instance type definition?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="True">Auto Scaling policy</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Auto Scaling group</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Auto Scaling tags</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Auto Scaling launch configuration</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>Which of the following are characteristics of Amazon VPC subnets? Choose 2 answers</p>
  <choiceresponse>
    <checkboxgroup>
      <choice correct="True">Each subnet spans at least 2 Availability Zones to provide a high-availability environment.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Each subnet maps to a single Availability Zone.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">CIDR block mask of/25 is the smallest range supported.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">By default, all subnets can route between each other, whether they are private or public.</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Instances in a private subnet can communicate with the Internet only if they have an Elastic IP.</choice>
    </checkboxgroup>
  </choiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>When you put objects in Amazon S3, what is the indication that an object was successfully stored?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="True">A HTTP 200 result code and MD5 checksum, taken together, indicate that the operation was successful.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Amazon S3 is engineered for 99.999999999% durability. Therefore there is no need to confirm that data was inserted.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">A success code is inserted into the S3 object metadata.</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Each S3 account has a special bucket named _s3_logs. Success codes are written to this bucket with a timestamp and checksum.</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>A Provisioned IOPS volume must be at least __________ GB in size</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">1</choice>
      <choice correct="False">50</choice>
      <choice correct="False">20</choice>
      <choice correct="True">10</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
<problem>
  <p>You have a video transcoding application running on Amazon EC2. Each instance polls a queue to find out which video should be transcoded, and then runs a transcoding process. If this process is interrupted, the video will be transcoded by another instance based on the queuing system. You have a large backlog of videos which need to be transcoded and would like to reduce this backlog by adding more instances. You will need these instances only until the backlog is reduced. Which type of Amazon EC2 instances should you use to reduce the backlog in the most cost efficient way?</p>
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <choicegroup type="MultipleChoice" shuffle="True">
      <choice correct="False">Reserved instances</choice>
      <choice correct="True">Spot instances</choice>
      <choice correct="False">Dedicated instances</choice>
      <choice correct="False">On-demand instances</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
</problem>
